What are you doing?
Why do you look like that?
[THUDS]
Let's go.
Who gave you the right
to interfere with my affairs?
We are just businessmen
closing a deal,
so now, let's begin
the transaction.
Wait, you'll face two big
syndicates.
Only four of you
are storming in?
This handoff is quick,
but we still planned it.
[MULTIPLE GUNFIRE]
What was that?
DDE! Open the door!
Damn you, Zoey! I trusted you!
You still have time to change,
Francis, surrender now!
You're the ones who should
surrender!
You entered the wrong den!
They shouldn't get away.
I didn't know you were
that good at fighting, Joey.
My father taught me.
Thank you for saving me.
I'm just doing my job.
Francis Toledo,
you are under arrest.
The DDE raided the transaction
in Valmora.
The items and money were seized.
Everything was lost.
Boss is wounded.
Why, Boss?
One of my cufflinks is missing.
A person too private is often
hiding many things.
Why don't you like Sir Tomas?
Just remember,
do not trust Tomas.
Do you have news?
I'm sick of their excuses
about your father's corpse.
I wanted to tell you something.
What's the problem?
[GATE CREAKS]
What is that?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Some truths are dangerous
to deliver.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
You've made enemies,
and if something were
to happen to you,
they wouldn't be surprised.
Mom?
Andrew...
What are you doing here?
You might get cold.
I'm just getting some air.
What brought you here?
I brought your favorite cake.
I'm sure you miss this.
That's what I used to send
to your office.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Of course, I remember.
Thank you, son.
You're welcome, Mom.
You know,
before, you always told me
that when you got a job,
you'd always bring me this.
And I told you...
"How? You're stubborn.
You won't get a job."
Look at me now, Mom.
I have a career.
And did you know...
I followed your footsteps
because...
I wanted you to be proud of me?
I promise you, Mom,
I won't use my profession
for selfishness.
And of course,
I carry your name.
So, I will never taint it.
Mom, did you know...
the case I'm handling now
is the biggest drug syndicate
here in the Philippines,
Berdugo?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
And, Mom, I'm close.
I'll meet him,
and I'll use everything
I learned from you
to expose him and make him pay
for all his crimes.
My child...
Wait...
What will you do?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Child, wait. Hey, dear, wait.
Call the police.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR RATTLING]
Joey!
Dad...
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Miguel?
Miguel...
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom...
Are you okay?
Yeah,
I'm okay.
I'm just happy about...
what you're doing.
Because I never thought...
that you'd turn your life around
like this.
Son, you might overdo it.
No, Mom.
You know what, Mom?
Let's go inside,
you might catch the dew here.
Okay.
Let's go?
All right.
Let's go, Mom.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Miguel.
Wait.
You're alive?
Joey, your father is here.
Mom, I'm sorry,
I've known for a long time.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I was going to tell you.
I was going to tell you earlier.
Sorry for keeping it secret.
It's okay, dear.
I understand.
Just don't do it again.
How can I?
When there's no room for anger
in my heart now.
I'm just happy you're here,
Miguel.
You're alive.
Thank you so much
for understanding, Clarissa.
I don't understand.
Why did you have to pretend you
were dead?
Because if I'm dead,
no one will look for me.
I can move more freely
to find Berdugo,
and you won't be in danger.
It's alarming.
The drug situation
keeps escalating.
And the masterminds
they seem to be slipping away.
So, be careful,
because people like that don't
forget names and faces.
Brother's here.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Hon, let's eat.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN FIRING]
Castro, let's go!
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew was telling me
about his coverage in the north.
Drug deal.
Unfortunately,
the mastermind escaped again.
Yeah.
How about you, Tomas?
How are you?
Busy? Where did you come from?
From a meeting.
How was it?
Was the deal finalized?
Unfortunately, not.
There was interference.
A client withdrew.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Well, that's business.
There will be others, Hon.
Yeah, but the one who interfered
must pay.
Tomas, is that blood?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, does the chief know
about your plan
to show yourself to mom?
Yes.
I asked permission. He knows.
Does this mean you'll reveal
yourself?
We'll be together again?
No, dear.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I need to finish the mission.
I only came here to see you.
I don't want to see you hurt,
Clarissa.
I promise, after this mission,
Berdugo will be imprisoned
and our family will finally
be complete.
Clarissa, we're almost there.
Joey, we're close.
I hope so.
I hope this is it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why, Hon?
Where were you wounded?
There was...
a branch on the driveway.
I wasn't looking.
Hon, you have to be careful.
That has to be cleaned.
- Let me help you.
- It's okay, it's okay.
I got this.
I'll just change the bandage.
Don't leave Andrew.
He rarely eats with company.
Okay.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Tomas is really...
He hates being fussed over.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why?
What's wrong, Andrew?
Sister, it's not just a small
wound.
Brother's wound is deep.
You better talk to him
or at least observe him.
What do you mean?
Maybe he has a problem
he doesn't want to tell us.
Okay.
I'll talk to him.
And I really appreciate
your concern for Tomas.
You were right.
It was Berdugo who made
the deal in the north.
I even heard Delilah
mention his alias.
We need to talk
because next time,
you'll be the one I'll speak to.
But of course, if you permit,
Berdugo.
Certainly.
It's just frustrating.
I was there for so long,
I didn't see his face.
Child, don't worry.
That's okay.
What matters is you're alive.
I was so worried about you.
I wanted to help,
but I couldn't do anything.
That's why I just texted you
earlier.
Yes, Dad.
But why did it seem like only
DDE agents were there?
There were no police.
Sir, positive.
Berdugo is at the resort.
Why aren't the other police
moving?
Because we also have
confirmation
that one of our men is involved
in the syndicate, it's Castro.
It is a bad enough image
for the police.
We need to compartmentalize
the operation
so no information leaks.
That's why no police,
only DDE agents.
But, Sir...
Miguel, don't attempt
to charge in.
You'll waste everything
you've worked for.
Do not blow your cover,
Major Delgado.
That's an order!
I wanted to tell you and Andrew,
but I couldn't.
There's protocol.
Does Andrew know about this?
He has to, he's in media.
He hasn't mentioned anything
to me.
His agent friend, Zoey,
knows a lot.
Gosh, Andrew.
You didn't even tell me
you were back,
then suddenly you call
for a meeting?
What if I had a date?
Wait, you actually have a date?
Just "what if," Boss.
Anyway, the reason I called
for a meeting
is because I want
to walk you through
what happened in the north.
I want us aligned
because starting tomorrow,
that's where our coverage
will revolve.
Confirmed.
Berdugo was there.
That's him.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
He's handsome, isn't he?
What?
But that's just his back.
The shot is far,
and he's wearing a hat.
How do we build a case
with that?
No face, no profile.
Your ex-lover slash TOTGA
in DDE, Boss,
she has no visual ID?
None.
But...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I found this.
I found this when Berdugo
was escaping.
Looks expensive.
Exactly.
Men like him
don't wear generic things.
And high-end accessories
are easier to trace
because there are fewer
suppliers.
Yes.
So, we don't chase the man.
We chase his tastes.
Yes.
Can I see it, Boss.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's an engraving...
A brand?
Well, that's what I thought too.
But I tried reverse searching.
Nothing, no brand identified.
Are we sure this is a brand?
Men like Berdugo,
they're narcissistic.
This could be initials.
Even their towels have initials.
Possible, possible, yes.
And Joey, wasn't she with you
on this mission?
Does she know about this
cufflink?
Not yet.
I owe her.
So, while this isn't solid,
she doesn't have to know.
She needs answers.
She doesn't need another risk.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Nothing was explained to me.
I can't just stand idle.
So, when I learned Berdugo
was selling drugs to Delilah,
I searched it in this notebook.
Here, I found it.
Lumen-X?
I heard that from them.
Yes, that's a party drug.
Popular among the youth.
What is this?
Why is there a drawing of a
mushroom with "2019" written?
Maybe Ramon made this
because Lumen-X has a component
from magic mushrooms.
The effect is potent.
You'll hallucinate.
That's why I did surveillance
on underground sellers
of magic mushrooms.
Maybe it would lead me
to Berdugo's laboratory.
Did you find it?
No.
But I won't stop
until they're imprisoned.
My fellow Tirada viewers,
Lumen-X is the drug destroying
the lives of the youth today.
This man with his back turned...
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's Berdugo,
the creator of this damn drug.
He escaped the operation
in the north,
but I'm certain his world
is shrinking.
And next time,
there will be no escape.
It's prison time.
You can count on it,
fellow Tirada viewers.
As always.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Okay.
- Nice. Solid.
Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful.
[CHUCKLES]
I thought I was brave,
but that's the real courage
of Boss Idol.
[CHUCKLES]
Just passionate.
Ma'am Zoey, he's not only
passionate in tirades...
if you know what I mean.
Hey, gross!
Why?
In love! Passionate in...
Right? Love, right?
- Love?
- Right, Boss?
Yes, good thing you clarified.
And besides, we're not even sure
if it's the right "oey"
we're teasing.
Yes, true. Sounds like it.
This one, Zoey.
The other one...
Oey?
So clever.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Okay, okay. Are you happy now?
Just joking, Boss.
You're teasing me again.
It's just a joke.
Anyway, you two, if it's okay,
step out for now,
especially you.
Be careful,
you might lose your job.
All right, I'm going, I'm going.
We'll leave you for now.
Boss...
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
Do you think Andrew suspected
anything?
He didn't ask anything directly.
But I saw he was contemplating.
But since we're brothers-in-law,
he won't think I'm Berdugo.
That idea is too far
of what I am to him.
But, Boss, he's getting closer
and closer.
I know.
And he's smart.
Once he smells something,
he won't let go.
Like I said, he's obsessed.
If he won't stop,
then we must push harder.
Boss, the operation cannot stop.
Boss, I don't mean to get ahead
of you,
but there's only one question
you need to answer.
Which is more important?
Andrew...
or your business?
Sorry about that, okay?
It's fine.
I didn't know they were aware
of whatever you
and Joey have.
That's nothing.
They link me to everyone anyway.
We're all single.
[ZOEY CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
What brought you here?
Since the operation
in the north is over,
I just want to apologize
for how things went.
If I made you or Joey
uncomfortable.
Since we're talking
about this again,
I need to clarify something.
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING]
About?
Anyway,
just check the new batch
of Lumen-X.
You're not coming?
I don't want to be late
for my meeting.
I trust you and Lisa.
I thought you wanted
to see it too?
And to answer your question,
nothing is more important to me
than my family,
and the business
that sustains us.
Find a way to get rid of him.
No trace, no noise.
My pleasure, Boss.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you remember the brown
stuffed bear?
Why do you need that?
It's not for you.
You know, girl, try this.
Crispy mushroom.
Did you get what I sent?
The logo and the number
in Ramon's notebook.
Won't this be a hindrance
to our operation?
If sabotage was my intention...
I'm not talking to you!
So many operations
have already failed.
What are you doing there
in Sta. Isabel?
Sir, I feel Berdugo's laboratory
is here.
Ma'am Yvette said she'll have me
brought there.
But I'm thinking...
What about you?
I'll bring Joey there.
Tell her who you really are.